<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>UK on</title><link>https://doks-child-theme.netlify.app/docs/uk/</link><description>Recent content in UK on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://doks-child-theme.netlify.app/docs/uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cambridge</title><link>https://doks-child-theme.netlify.app/docs/uk/cambridge/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://doks-child-theme.netlify.app/docs/uk/cambridge/</guid><description>Recommended Places to Visit #
Bath is a city on the River Cam in eastern England. It occupies an area of 40.7 km². It is home to the University of Cambridge, which contains exhibits on archaeology and anthropology, polar exploration, the history of science and zoology.
Trinity College, St. John’s College, King’s College #
👉 These are the most aesthetic Colleges! Trinity College, St. John&amp;rsquo;s College and King&amp;rsquo;s College are constituent colleges of the University of Cambridge.</description></item><item><title>Jurassic Coast</title><link>https://doks-child-theme.netlify.app/docs/uk/jurassic-coast/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://doks-child-theme.netlify.app/docs/uk/jurassic-coast/</guid><description>Recommended Places to Visit #
The Jurassic Coast stretches from Exmouth in East Devon to Studland Bay in Dorset, a distance of about 96 miles, and was inscribed on the World Heritage List in mid-December 2001.
Old Harry Rocks #
👉 A must see. Old Harry Rocks are three chalk formations, including a stack and a stump, located at Handfast Point, on the Isle of Purbeck in Dorset, southern England.</description></item><item><title>Peak District</title><link>https://doks-child-theme.netlify.app/docs/uk/peak-district/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://doks-child-theme.netlify.app/docs/uk/peak-district/</guid><description>Recommended Places to Visit #
The Peak District forms the southern extremity of the Pennines. Much of it is upland above 1,000 feet (300 m), its highest point being Kinder Scout at 2,087 ft (636 m).
Town of Tideswell #
Walking around Tideswell, especially St John’s Church and its surroundings is nice.
More Information →
Town of Bakewell #
Walking around the River Wye is nice.
More Information →
Chatsworth House #
Bakewell DE45 1PP.</description></item><item><title>Scotland Road Trip</title><link>https://doks-child-theme.netlify.app/docs/uk/scotland-road-trip/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://doks-child-theme.netlify.app/docs/uk/scotland-road-trip/</guid><description>Itinerary Outline #
Day Location Overnight 1 Edinburgh Edinburgh 2 Forth Bridge, Loch Level, Pitlorchy Pitlorchy 3 Inverness, Loch Ness, Skye Skye 4 Skye Skye 5 Fort William, Glenfinnan, Glencoe Onich 6 Glencoe, Loch Lomond, Glasgow Glasgow 7 Glasgow Glasgow Itinerary Inspiration →
Day 1 #
Reach London Kings Cross early in the morning before 08:52 departure to Edinburgh Waverley.
Arrive at Edinburgh Waverley at 13:10 (4 h 18 min journey).</description></item><item><title>Bath</title><link>https://doks-child-theme.netlify.app/docs/uk/bath/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://doks-child-theme.netlify.app/docs/uk/bath/</guid><description>Recommended Places to Visit #
Bath is a sprawling city of slightly above a hundred thousand in population and is 97 miles west of London.
The Roman Baths #
👉 You have to see this, it is what you came to Bath for! Once the site of one of the great religious spas of the ancient world. People of Roman Britain came to the site to worship and bathe in the waters of the natural thermal springs, which still flow with hot water today.</description></item></channel></rss>