<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Europe on</title><link>https://icsstravel.netlify.app/docs/europe/</link><description>Recent content in Europe on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://icsstravel.netlify.app/docs/europe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Italy</title><link>https://icsstravel.netlify.app/docs/europe/italy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 15:22:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://icsstravel.netlify.app/docs/europe/italy/</guid><description>Itinerary #
Day Location Overnight 1 Arrival into Pisa Pisa 2 Pisa Pisa 3 Florence Florence 4 Rome Rome 5 Rome Rome 6 Amalfi Coast Sorrento 7 Amalfi Coast Sorrento 8 Pompeii, Naples Naples 9 Naples, Bologna Bologna 10 Venice Venice 11 Burano, Venice London Getting Around #
Train Timetable and Tickets → Trains in Italy Guide →
Freccia, Italo: Better to book in advance to save money.
Regional, Intercity: Can buy at the station.</description></item><item><title>Paris and Nice</title><link>https://icsstravel.netlify.app/docs/europe/paris-nice/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 15:22:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://icsstravel.netlify.app/docs/europe/paris-nice/</guid><description>Itinerary #
Day Location Overnight 1 Paris Paris 2 Paris Paris 3 Versailles (Day Trip) Nice 4 Nice and Monaco Nice 5 Nice and Villefranche-sur-Mer Nice 6 Nice London Paris Dining Tips →
Day 1 #
Arrive at St Pancras no later than 07:00 for Eurostar to Paris.
Arrive at Paris Gare du Nord at 11:57. Go to Hotel de l&amp;rsquo;Aqueduc to drop off bag before check-in, and get lunch.</description></item><item><title>Berlin</title><link>https://icsstravel.netlify.app/docs/europe/berlin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 13:26:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://icsstravel.netlify.app/docs/europe/berlin/</guid><description>Accommodation #
Generator Berlin Mitte Oranienburger Strasse 65, Mitte, Berlin, 10117, Germany
Bring a towel and toiletries!
Getting to Accommodation from Airport #
Take S-Bahn S9 line from S Flughafen Berlin-Schönefeld Bhf to S Hackescher Markt (13 stops, in direction of S Spandau Bhf)
Take tram M1 line from S Hackescher Markt to Berlin Oranienburger Straße (2 stops, in direction of Mitte, Am Kupfergraben)
Walk to accomodation
Total 55 min</description></item><item><title>Copenhagen and Malmo</title><link>https://icsstravel.netlify.app/docs/europe/copenhagen-malmo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://icsstravel.netlify.app/docs/europe/copenhagen-malmo/</guid><description>Itinerary #
Day 1 #
Time Activity Remarks 0500 Be at Paddington Station for Easybus Bus at 0515, if reached early can aim to go for the 0445 bus 0650 Reach airport, clear check-in 0900 Flight to Copenhagen 1100 Reach Copenhagen, Clear Immigration 1200 Take Metro to City. From Koebenhavns Lufthavn st (Airport) Station, take Train 029 towards Nivå St. for 3 stops to Copenhagen Central Station. Buy tickets at metro.</description></item></channel></rss>